scvngr.com 2019-09-12

# Privacy Policy | LevelUp | Mobile Ordering, Restaurant Loyalty, Customer Engagement, and CRM

## Privacy Policy

### 1\. Introduction

This Privacy Policy explains to Users of the LevelUp website (https://www.thelevelup.com/), mobile applications offered by LevelUp and/or applications offered by third-parties integrated to the LevelUp platform ("LevelUp Apps"), microsites, software and services (collectively, the "Service"), how SCVNGR, Inc., doing business as LevelUp ("LevelUp", "we" or "us"), gathers and uses information collected in connection with use of the Service and LevelUp Apps. LevelUp takes reasonable steps to protect User privacy consistent with the guidelines set forth in this Privacy Policy and with all applicable laws. In this Privacy Policy, "User" or "you" means any person using the Service, whether by browsing the LevelUp website or installing or using LevelUp App, paying for items and/or transactions through LevelUp using a LevelUp App, engaging in loyalty and rewards programs ("Programs") offered by LevelUp merchants (each a "Merchant"), or participating in any other activities available through the Service. 

BY ACCESSING OR USING THE SERVICE AND ANY LEVELUP APP, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTAND, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND OUR USER TERMS OF SERVICE (https://www.thelevelup.com/user-terms). IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS, DO NOT USE THE SERVICE. 

### 2\. First Up, We Want You to Know This:

You control your Personal Information on the LevelUp platform. We will never disclose your email address, transaction history, or other Personal Information to any Merchant or any other third party for their marketing purposes without you first authorizing that Merchant or third party to access such information. This allows you to use the LevelUp Service and LevelUp Apps without receiving a whole lot of direct marketing you don't want. 

You can authorize LevelUp to provide your Personal Information to a Merchant by logging into a Merchant or third-party mobile LevelUp App, or by expressly acknowledging a request from a LevelUp App for permission to access your information on the LevelUp platform. You can revoke these permissions at any time by logging into the LevelUp website at https://www.thelevelup.com/login. 

LevelUp will never share your Financial Information (i.e., your credit or debit card information) with anyone other than the payment processor that we use to charge your card (Braintree, a division of PayPal, Inc.). 

### 3\. Why Do We Have This Privacy Policy?

All companies that you do business with choose whether and how they want to share your Personal Information and other information. Federal law gives you the right to limit some, but not all, of that sharing. Federal law also requires companies to tell you how they collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do. 

### 4\. What Information Do We Collect?

Personal Information: LevelUp collects some of your identifying information in connection with the Service, depending on how you use the Service. When you create a LevelUp User Account (whether through a LevelUp App or the LevelUp website), pay via LevelUp, engage in a Program, submit content to LevelUp, complete a survey, send us feedback, request information about the Service, apply for a job, or sign up for special offers from third parties, LevelUp may collect information from you, which could include the following (collectively, "Personal Information"): 

  * first and last name 
  * mailing address 
  * email address 
  * telephone number 
  * date of birth 
  * location 
  * dietary preferences 
  * merchant transaction and Program data (including the amount, date, and location of the transaction, the amount of credit earned and redeemed, and the identity and amount of items purchased), and 
  * non-Financial Information related to your payment instruments, such as expiration date. 

You do not have to provide Personal Information to LevelUp, but you may not be able to take advantage of all features of the Service if you do not. 

Financial Information: In order to use the Service and the LevelUp platform to initiate LevelUp transactions at partner merchants, you will need to link a payment instrument, such as a debit or credit card account number, to your LevelUp User Account ("Financial Information"). LevelUp will only collect Financial Information from Users using a secure, transparent pass through to our third-party data vault and payment gateway provider (Braintree), and LevelUp will never store your Financial Information itself. LevelUp and its providers maintain compliance with all laws and rules protecting the privacy of your financial information, including the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). 

Web/Mobile Tracking Information: LevelUp and its third-party service providers may use web and/or mobile tracking technologies, such as cookies, beacons, pixel tags and clear GIFs, to collect data related to usage of the Service, the Programs, and web and email marketing conducted by or on behalf of LevelUp. Such data may include: 

  * the address of the websites you visited before and after you visited the Service, 
  * the type of browser you are using, 
  * your Internet Protocol (IP) address, 
  * what pages in the Service you visit and what links you clicked on, 
  * the identification for advertising associated with your iOS or Android device, and 
  * identifiers of beacons communicated to a LevelUp App. 

In order to collect Web/Mobile Tracking Information and to make your use of the Service more efficient, we may store cookies on your device. LevelUp and third party contractors engaged to provide services on behalf of LevelUp ("Contractors") may also use web tracking technologies that are placed in web pages on the Service or in email communications to collect information about actions that users take when they interact with the Service or such email communications. Web Tracking Information is not correlated by LevelUp to individual users. Mobile Tracking information may be correlated to individual Users. Some Web Tracking Information may include data, such as IP address data, that is unique to you. You may be able to modify your browser settings to alter which web tracking technologies are permitted when you use the Service, but this may affect the performance of the Service. 

### 5\. How Does LevelUp Use and Share Your Information?

All companies need to share users personal information to run their everyday business. In this section, we explain the reasons that companies can share their customers' personal information; the reasons LevelUp chooses to share information; and whether you can limit this sharing. 

Personal Information: LevelUp will use and store your Personal Information to deliver the LevelUp Service to you (including charges, receipts, rewards tracking and notifications, and system notifications); to market customer rewards to you; to improve our products and services; to investigate (and remedy) fraudulent or allegedly fraudulent activity; and to perform aggregated data analysis. Additionally, any Personal Information that we collect via Facebook will be used for open graph posts. 

LevelUp does not sell or rent its mailing list, and we will not disclose your email address to any third party for marketing purposes, unless you specifically authorize a third party (such as a LevelUp Merchant or third-party LevelUp App provider) to access your information. LevelUp will disclose your Personal Information to third parties only in the following limited circumstances: 

  * When you use the LevelUp Service at a Merchant, LevelUp may disclose your partial name (first name and last initial, but not your email address) and the transaction details (location, amount) to the associated Merchant to aid in the utilization process and loyalty program tracking; 
  * LevelUp may allow our Contractors who are performing marketing services, delivering goods, administering promotions, analyzing data and usage of the Service, processing credit card payments, operating the Service or providing support and maintenance services for the Service, or providing customer service, to access Personal Information. We require Contractors to use the Personal Information they access only in connection with the services they perform for LevelUp, and never for any marketing or other purposes. LevelUp Contractors will always be required to maintain the confidentiality of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 
  * LevelUp will permit access to your Personal Information by a Merchant or third-party that you specifically authorize to access your information, either by granting a party's express request for permissions in a LevelUp App, or by downloading and logging into a LevelUp app with your LevelUp credentials, which grants to the Merchant providing the LevelUp App permission to access your Personal Information, including the email address you use to log in, and your transaction history. You can revoke access permissions granted to any Merchant or other third-party at any time by logging in to the LevelUp website at: https://www.thelevelup.com/login; 
  * If you are a winner of a Merchant or LevelUp sponsored competition (as detailed in the Applicable Contest Terms), we will share your contact information for purposes of prize fulfillment only. 

Financial Information: LevelUp will only ever use your Financial Information for the purpose of submitting an authorized charge to your payment instrument, in accordance with LevelUp's User Terms. Financial Information is never provided to LevelUp in unencrypted form, or stored by LevelUp. Your Financial Information is never disclosed to third parties, including LevelUp Merchants, other than LevelUp's data vault and payment gateway provider (Braintree). 

Aggregate Information: LevelUp may also use Personal Information to create aggregated data for analytical purposes. This statistical information does not contain any individual identifying information or contact information and is used to understand our customer base as a whole and to better serve our market. LevelUp reserves the right to share such aggregated, non-identifiable data with 3rd parties. 

Web/Mobile Tracking Information: LevelUp uses Web and Mobile Tracking Information to administer the Service (including to deliver notifications to users), to understand how well our Service is working, and to develop aggregate, statistical information on usage of the Services. LevelUp may disclose Web and/or Mobile Tracking Information, without individual identifying Personal Information (or with such information if you have specifically authorized the disclosure of Personal Information to that party), to third party advertisers and advertising agencies, Merchants, third party LevelUp App providers, and Contractors, in order for LevelUp and such third parties to analyze the performance of the Services and the behavior of users, to operate and improve the Service. 

Email Communications: If you create a LevelUp User Account and provide your email address, we will send you administrative and promotional emails concerning the LevelUp Service and LevelUp platform, including new features, promotions, Programs, and rewards. If you wish to opt out of promotional emails, you may do so by following the "unsubscribe" instructions in the email, by contacting LevelUp Support, or by editing your LevelUp User Account settings as described below. All LevelUp Users receive administrative emails. If you wish to opt out of administrative emails, you must delete your account entirely and cease use of the Service. 

Network Operators: Use of the Service may involve use of the services of third party telecommunications carriers and service providers (such as the services of the carrier that provides cell phone service to you). Such carriers and service providers are not LevelUp's Contractors, and any information that a carrier collects in connection with your use of the Service is not Personal Information and is not subject to this Privacy Policy. LevelUp is not responsible for the acts or omissions of telecommunications carriers or service providers. 

Additional Disclosures: Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Privacy Policy, LevelUp reserves the right to use or disclose Personal Information and any other information LevelUp collects in connection with the Service: (a) to any successor to LevelUp's business, including as a result of any merger, acquisition, asset sale or similar transaction; (b) to any law enforcement, judicial authority, or governmental or regulatory authority, to the extent required by law or legal process; or (c) if in LevelUp's reasonable discretion, such use or disclosure is necessary to enforce or protect LevelUp's legal rights or to protect the legal rights of third parties. 

### 6\. Privacy Settings/Opt Out

If you would like your Personal Information permanently removed from our database, or your Financial Information removed from Levelup's data vault provider, please contact us at [support@thelevelup.com](mailto:support@thelevelup.com) or 1-855-538-3542. We will promptly disable your LevelUp User Account and you will no longer receive email from LevelUp. Your removal from the mailing list or database will not remove records of past transactions or delete information stored in our data backups and archives, as required by law. Data on past transactions and data stored in backups and archives will be deleted in the normal course of LevelUp's business. You may elect to opt-out at any time after registering for the LevelUp service. 

### 7\. Third-Party LevelUp Apps

The LevelUp platform enables any third-party to develop applications, software, and websites that can access the LevelUp platform on your behalf, with your permission ("LevelUp Apps"). You may also be offered services, products and promotions provided by third parties as part of your use of any LevelUp App. 

Third-party LevelUp Apps interfacing with the LevelUp platform are required to be operated in accordance with LevelUp's Terms of Service for Merchants, Terms of Service for Developers, and this Privacy Policy, but they are not under the control of LevelUp, and LevelUp is not responsible for the contents of any linked site or third party app or third party LevelUp App. You will be responsible for reviewing and understanding any additional terms and conditions associated with any third party app, LevelUp App, sites, or services. Please remember that once you grant a third party or Merchant permission to access your Personal Information in the LevelUp platform, or you use a link to go from a LevelUp App or website to another website, LevelUp's Privacy Policy no longer restricts the use of such information by the third party, and you will then be subject to that Merchant's or that website's own rules and policies. You should make whatever investigation you feel necessary or appropriate before proceeding with any transaction with any of these third parties or granting permissions for any LevelUp App to access any of your Personal Information. LevelUp is not responsible for any claims, liabilities, losses, or damages suffered by you in connection with your use of a third party LevelUp App, site, or service, in connection with the LevelUp platform. 

### 8\. Access and Updating of Information

LevelUp encourages you to view your transaction history, and review and amend your email address or contact details, in the LevelUp platform at any time. Please contact us by sending an email to: [support@thelevelup.com](mailto:support@thelevelup.com) or by using your settings panel in your User Account accessible at: https://www.thelevelup.com/login. 

### 9\. General

Facebook Connect: If you connect to the LevelUp Service using Facebook Connect, you agree that any identifying information obtained by us by reason of your connection using Facebook Connect will constitute Personal Information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy, and you consent to our use and disclosure of such information in accordance with this Policy. If we stop using Facebook Connect as an access mechanism, you agree that we will nevertheless retain any Personal Information in accordance with this Policy. 

Security: We use reasonable security precautions to protect the security and integrity of your Personal Information in accordance with this Policy and all applicable laws. However, no Internet transmission is completely secure, and we cannot guarantee that security breaches will not occur. Without limitation of the foregoing, we are not responsible for the actions of hackers and other unauthorized third parties. 

Electronic Notice; Amendments: Pursuant to of LevelUp's User Terms, you agree to receive initial notice of this Privacy Policy, and all annual notices of the Privacy Policy, as amended from time to time, electronically. LevelUp may modify or amend this policy from time to time. We will notify you of these changes by posting the modified Privacy Policy, which will be available for review by you, on our website at https://www.thelevelup.com/privacy-policy. 

Children: LevelUp does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of the Service is directed at persons under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use the Service. If LevelUp learns that personally identifiable information of persons less than 13 years of age has been collected without verifiable parental consent, then LevelUp will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. To make such a request, please contact us at [support@thelevelup.com](mailto:support@thelevelup.com). 

Service Visitors from outside the United States: LevelUp and its servers are located in the United States and are subject to the applicable state and federal laws of the United States. If you choose to access or use the Service, you consent to the use and disclosure of information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and subject to such laws. 

### 10\. Google Analytics for Display Advertisers

LevelUp uses remarketing to advertise across the internet. Along with the Google Analytics cookie, the DoubleClick cookie is collected by Google Analytics based on your browsing history. This optimizes your ad exposure to be more targeted to your interests throughout the Google Display Network. This feature can be even more personalized, by letting you customize which ads you see. LevelUp follows the Google AdWords Remarketing Policy, as well as Google's restrictions for sensitive categories. If you decide that this isn't for you, feel free to visit [this page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) to opt out. 

### 11\. USA Patriot Act Notice to Merchants

To help the government fight the funding of terrorism and money laundering activities, federal law requires financial institutions to obtain, verify, and record information that identifies each person who registers for a Merchant Account with LevelUp. Merchants will be required to provide such information to the satisfaction of LevelUp prior to establishing a Merchant Account. 

Effective Date of this policy: July 16, 2015
